Alexander Graham Bell Family
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Subject File, ca. 1870-1970, n.d. (Box 143-327)
  - Deaf (Box 175)
    - Volta Bureau, Washington, D.C. (Box 204)
      - Reports, (2 folders)
    - Warren, Lillie Egington
    - Weeden, William P.
    - White, Andrew D.
    - White, Henry C.
    - Wines, Frederick H. For additional material see Container 175, Correspondence; Container 179, Census; and Container 222, Keller, Helen, Correspondence
    - Wright, John D.
    - Miscellany, (2 folders)
    - Printed matter, (1 folder) (Box 206)
  - Death of Alexander Graham Bell
    - Clippings, (3 folders); (4 folders) (Box 207, Box 208)
    - Editorial tributes, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 209)
    - Miscellany
    - Notes
    - Printed matter, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box 210)
  - Deland, Fred
    - Biography of Alexander Graham Bell, unpublished
    - Biography of Sarah Fuller, unpublished
    - Correspondence, 1877-1925, (2 folders) (Box 211)
    - Writings, (10 folders); (8 folders) (Box 212)
  - Dinners given by the Bells
  - District of Columbia
  - Drawings by Alexander Graham Bell
  - Electricity, bibliography (Box 213)
  - Eugenics
    - "A Few Thoughts Concerning Eugenics," by Alexander Graham Bell
    - Jordan, David Starr, excerpt
  - Evaporation experiments
  - Faber's talking machine
  - Fire alarm, electric
  - Genealogical Record Office, Washington, D.C. See also Containers 186 and 414-432, same heading
  - Genealogy of the Bell family
    - Bell family, St. Andrews, Scotland, (2 folders)
    - General correspondence
    - Greene ancestry
    - Hubbard ancestry
    - Miscellany, (3 folders) (Box 214)
    - Symonds ancestry
  - George Washington Memorial Association See Container 326, Washington (George) Memorial Association (Box 215)
  - Hanovarian (steamship), wreck of
  - Henry, Prince of Prussia
  - Heredity, (2 folders)
  - Historical Records Survey
  - Honors and awards, (9 folders); (17 folders); (30 folders); (1 folder) (Box 216, Box 217, Box 218)
  - Hubbard family genealogy, (5 folders)
  - Hubbard Memorial Hall, Washington, D.C.
  - Humor
  - Hydrodrome
    - Charts
    - Forlanini, Enrico (Box 219)
    - Meacham, William M. and Larned E.
    - Miscellany, (3 folders)
    - Patents
      - 1904-1919
      - 1919-1932, (3 folders) (Box 220)
    - Printed matter
    - "Ugly Duckling"
  - Impacts of experiments
  - Induction balance, (5 folders) (Box 221)
  - Itineraries
  - Jamestown Aeronautical Congress, Jamestown, Va., 1906-1907
  - Japan (Box 222)
  - Keller, Helen For additional material see Containers 81-83, Biography of Alexander Graham Bell
    - Biographical material
    - Correspondence, A-Z, (4 folders)
    - Miscellany
    - Poem, 1893
    - Printed matter
    - Trust fund (Box 223)
  - Kites and other aeronautical subjects See also Container 152, Kites, and Container 325, Tetrahedral kites
    - 1901, (2 folders)
    - 1901-1904, (3 folders) (Box 224)
    - 1903-1909, (3 folders) (Box 225)
    - "Kite Structure," by Alexander Graham Bell, from
      - National Geographic Magazine
  - Langley, Samuel P.
  - League of Nations
  - Longevity (Box 226)
    - Biographical data, 1910-1916, (6 folders) See also Containers 242-263, Statistical data, and Containers 414-431, same heading
    - Miscellany
      - "The Hyde Statistics"
      - Notes, (2 folders) (Box 227)
      - "Period of Birth"
    - Obituaries
      - 1911-1912, (3 folders)
      - 1912-1913, (3 folders) (Box 228)
      - 1913-1914, (3 folders) (Box 229)
      - 1914, (3 folders) (Box 230, Box 231, Box 232)
      - 1914-1915, (3 folders)
      - 1915, (3 folders) (Box 233, Box 234, Box 235, Box 236, Box 237, Box 238)
      - 1915-1916, (3 folders) (Box 239)
      - 1916, (4 folders) (Box 240)
      - 1916-1917, (4 folders) (Box 241)
    - Statistical data See also Containers 226 and 414-431, Biographical data (Box 242-262)
      - Index cards [unarranged; original order unknown]
      - Sheets (Box 263)
  - Longfellow Memorial Association (Box 264)
  - Magnetic telegraph
  - Marconi, Guglielmo
  - Martha's Vineyard, Mass., genealogies of families, (2 folders) See also Container 190, same heading
  - McCurdy, Arthur W., diary, 1899
  - Meteorological observations, Baddeck, Nova Scotia, Canada
  - Metric system
  - Motion
  - Movie, The Story of Alexander Graham Bell (Box 265)
    - Correspondence
      - Joy, Jason S.
      - Miscellaneous
    - Miscellany
    - Preview
      - Acceptances to attend, (5 folders)
      - Declinations to attend, A-Y, (2 folders) (Box 266)
      - Lists
        - Acceptances to attend
        - Declinations to attend
        - Invitees, (3 folders)
    - Scrapbook See Oversize (Box 267)
    - Typescripts
      - Final, (2 folders)
      - Revised
  - National Academy of Sciences, Washington, D.C.
  - National Geographic Magazine
  - National Geographic Society, Washington, D.C., (3 folders)
  - Patents
    - Apparatus for technical spelling
    - Copies, 1895-1918 (Box 268)
    - Decisions
    - Edison, Thomas A.
    - Lists, 1875-1913
  - Phonograph
    - American Graphaphone Co., (2 folders)
    - Bell, Charles James
    - Bell, Chichester Alexander
    - Correspondence, (3 folders)
    - Edison, Thomas A.
    - Hubbard, Gardiner Greene
    - Litigation
    - Miscellany (Box 269)
    - Patent
    - Printed matter, (3 folders)
    - Smithsonian Institution, Washington, D.C.
    - Tainter, Charles Sumner
    - Vail, Theodore N.
  - Photophones
    - Certificates of approval
    - Miscellany, (2 folders); (1 folder) See also Oversize (Box 270)
    - Patent, 1880-1881, (2 folders)
    - Patents, (2 folders)
  - Presidential inaugural committees
  - Radiant energy
  - Radiophone
  - Radium and cancer
  - Rain
  - Religion
  - Rockets (Box 271)
  - Royal Society (Great Britain)
  - Sable Island, Canada
  - Science
    - Cancelled checks
    - Early history, 1882-1968
  - Scientific American
  - Scientific notebooks
    - 1874-1876, (3 folders)
    - 1876-1893, (6 folders) See Oversize (Box 272)
    - 1897-1907, n.d., (5 folders) (Box 273)
  - Scientific notes, (1 folder) (Box 274)
  - Scientific study, "Contracts of Simple Matter" See Oversize
  - Selenium For additional material see Container 130, Greely, Adolphus W.
  - Shakespeare class
  - Sheep breeding records
    - Bell, Mabel Gardiner Hubbard, records, 1914-1922, (3 folders)
    - Catalogs, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 275)
    - Chronological file
      - 1884-1891, (5 folders)
      - 1891-1893, (5 folders) (Box 276)
      - 1893-1898, (7 folders) (Box 277)
      - 1899-1900, (5 folders) (Box 278)
      - 1901-1902, (6 folders) (Box 279)
      - 1903-1905, (5 folders) (Box 280)
      - 1907-1913, (8 folders) (Box 281)
      - 1913-1914, (5 folders) (Box 282)
      - 1914-1920, n.d., (6 folders) (Box 283)
    - Davidson, John, records
      - 1907-1910
      - 1914-1921, (3 folders) (Box 284)
    - Miscellany, (5 folders); (2 folders) (Box 285)
    - Printed matter
    - Statistics, 1910
  - Smithson, James
  - Smithsonian Institution, Washington, D.C.
    - Bicentennial of James Smithson's birth, 1965
    - Board of Regents
      - Correspondence
      - Letterbook, 1903 (Box 286)
    - Bureau of American Ethnology
    - Bust of Alexander Graham Bell
    - Deposit of experimental apparatus
    - Freer Gallery of Art, Washington, D.C.
    - Henry, Joseph, (2 folders)
    - Langley Laboratory for Aeronautics, Washington, D.C.
    - Langley Medal
    - Photocopied material (Box 287)
    - Printed matter, (2 folders)
    - Telephone exhibit
  - Stamps commemorating Alexander Graham Bell
  - Subaquatic projectiles
  - Tainter, Charles Sumner
  - Telegraph
    - Bill, England, 1878
    - Green, Norvin (Box 288)
    - Miscellany
    - Multiple telegraph
    - Postal telegraph
    - Regulations in Congress
    - Western Union Telegraph Co.
  - Telephone
    - Correspondence, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 289)
    - Advertising
    - Agreements
    - American Bell Telephone Co., (5 folders); (2 folders) (Box 290)
    - Australia, 1910
    - Barker, George, 1888
    - Barrett, William F.
    - Bell Telephone Co.
    - Bell Telephone of Canada, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 291)
    - Bell Telephone Memorial
    - Berliner, Emile
    - Bourseul, Charles
    - Brooks, David
    - Brown, George
    - Carty, John J. For additional material see Container 64, Death of Alexander Graham Bell
    - Cincinnati, Ohio, telephone directory, 1883 (Box 292)
    - Correspondence relating to telephone companies
    - Deposition of Alexander Graham Bell
    - Diagrams
    - Dominion Telegraph Co.
    - Drawing of the telephone by Alexander Graham Bell See also Container 318, Telephone bell, and Container 320, Telephone switchboard
    - Eastern Telegraph Co.
    - Electric telephone
    - Ellis, Alexander John For additional material see Containers 81-83, Biography of Alexander Graham Bell, and Containers 201-203, Visible speech
    - Emery, J. Herbert
    - Experimental notebook (Box 293)
    - Experiments in Great Britain
    - Extracts from correspondence and published sources re the telephone
    - Field, Kate
    - Foreign countries
    - Fox, Caroline
    - France
    - Gifford, Walter S.
    - Gilliland Electric Manufacturing Co.
    - Gray, Elisha, (2 folders)
    - Helmoltz, Hermann von
    - Henry, Joseph
    - Hitz, John
    - Improvements to the telephone
    - International Bell Telephone Co.
    - Italy (Box 294)
    - Langdon, William C.
    - Lightning
    - Litigation
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Abstracts of evidence
      - American Bell Tel. Co. v. Dolbear, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box 295)
      - American Bell Tel. Co. v. Eaton
      - American Bell Tel. Co. v. Overland Tel. Co. of New Jersey, (2 folders)
      - American Bell Tel. Co. v. Spencer
      - American Bell Tel. Co. v. People's Tel. Co. (Box 296)
        - Drawbaugh case, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 297, Box 298, Box 299, Box 300, Box 301)
        - Various suits (Box 302)
        - Bell Tel. Co. v. Dowd, (1 folder) (Box 303)
      - Brooks, David, patent for telephone circuits
      - Conkling, Roscoe, appellate oral arguments
      - Dickerson, E. N., argument for American Bell Telephone (Box 304)
        - Co.
      - Edison, Thomas A.
      - Garland, Augustus H., Alexander Graham Bell's letters to
      - Gray, Elisha, (2 folders)
      - Pan-Electric Telephone Co., (1 folder) (Box 305, Box 306)
      - Patents, (1 folder) (Box 307)
      - Reis, Philipp
      - The Speaking Telephone Interferences, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 308, Box 309)
      - Storrow, J. J.
        - Correspondence, 1877-1896
        - Proofs by and about Alexander Graham Bell
          - Vol. 1
          - Vol. 2 (Box 310)
      - Telephone appeals
        - Drawbaugh
        - Reis
      - United States v. American Bell Tel. Co., (3 folders); (9 folders) (Box 311, Box 312)
      - Western Union Tel. Co. v. American Bell Tel. Co., (1 folder); (5 folders) (Box 313)
    - Liverpool Telephone Co. (Box 314)
    - Long distance lines
    - Maynard, George C.
    - McCurdy, Richard A.
    - Michelson, Albert
    - Microphone, D. E. Hugh's
    - National Bell Telephone Co.
    - New England Telephone and Telegraph Co.
    - Norway
    - Notes and drawings
    - Oriental Bell Telephone Co., London, England, (3 folders) (Box 315)
    - Patents
      - Belgium
      - Brazil
      - Brown, William M.
      - England
      - France
      - Miscellany, (2 folders); (12 folders) (Box 316, Box 317)
      - Printed matter, (4 folders)
      - Statement re Thomas Sanders and Gardiner G. Hubbard
      - Uruguay
    - Pedro II, emperor of Brazil
    - Phonautograph
    - Providence Group (Box 318)
    - Rogers, Harriet B. For additional material see Containers 210-212, Deland, Fred
    - Scientific articles, extracts from
    - Scientific notes, 1877-1878, (2 folders)
    - Specifications See also Oversize
    - Tainter, Charles Sumner
    - Telephone bell, Alexander Graham Bell's drawing See also Container 292, Drawings, and Container 320, Telephone switchboard
    - Telephone Co., London, England, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box 319)
    - Telephone exchange
    - Telephone Pioneers of America, (2 folders)
    - Telephone studies, (3 folders) (Box 320)
    - Telephone switchboard, Alexander Graham Bell's drawing See also Container 292, Drawings, and Container 318, Telephone bell
    - Thompson, Silvanus P. (Box 321)
    - Toronto Telephone Despatch Co.
    - Transcontinental telephone
    - Tropical American Telephone Co.
    - Underground telephone wires
    - United States International Exhibition, Philadelphia, Pa., 1876
    - United Telephone Co.
    - Victoria, Queen of Great Britain See also Oversize
    - Watson, Thomas A.
    - Wines, Frederick H. For additional material see Container 175, Correspondence; Container 179, Census; and Container 222, Keller, Helen, Correspondence
    - Wireless telephony
    - Miscellany
    - Printed matter, (2 folders); (8 folders); (4 folders); (6 folders) (Box 322, Box 323, Box 324, Box 325)
  - Tetrahedral kites See also Containers 152 and 223, Kites
  - Vibrations
  - Ware, John F. W. (Box 326)
  - Washington (George) Memorial Association, (2 folders)
  - Wednesday evening receptions
    - Correspondence
    - Guest books, (2 folders) (Box 327)
    - List of names
  - Western Union Telegraph Co.
  - Woman's suffrage
- Beinn Bhreagh Recorder, 1909-1922 (Box 328-345)
  Bound volumes of the Beinn Bhreagh Recorder, a bulletin written and distributed by Alexander Graham Bell and his associates.
  - General (Box 328)
  - Vol. 1, 1909
  - Vol. 2, 1909-1910
  - Vol. 3, 1910 (Box 329)
  - Vol. 4, 1910 (Box 330)
  - Vol. 5, 1910
  - Vol. 6, 1910 (Box 331)
  - Vol. 7, 1910 (Box 332)
  - Vol. 8, 1911
  - Vol. 9, 1911-1912 (Box 333)
  - Vol. 10, 1912
  - Vol. 11, 1912 (Box 334)
  - Vol. 12, 1912-1913
  - Vol. 13, 1913 (Box 335)
  - Vol. 14, 1913-1914
  - Vol. 15, 1914 (Box 336)
  - Vol. 16, 1914
  - Vol. 17, 1914-1915 (Box 337)
  - Vol. 18, 1915 (Box 338)
  - Vol. 19, 1916
  - Vol. 20, 1916 (Box 339)
  - Vol. 21, 1917-1918
  - Vol. 22, 1918-1919 (Box 340)
  - Vol. 23, 1919
  - Vol. 24, 1919-1921 (Box 341)
  - Vol. 25, 1921-1922
  - Miscellany
  - Index
    - Sheets
    - Indexes (Box 342)
      - Vols. I-VIII
      - Vols. IX-XVII (Box 343)
      - Vols. XVIII-XX (Box 344)
      - Subject
        - A-N
        - O-Z (Box 345)
- Scientific Notebooks, 1879-1922, n.d. (Box 346-395)
  Notebooks divided into two groups, home notes and laboratory notes. Arranged chronologically thereunder. See Microfilm series for microfilm editions of the home notes and some of the laboratory notes.
  - Home notes See also Microfilm (Box 346)
    - Vol. 1, 6 Dec. 1879-3 June 1880
    - Vol. 2, 10 Oct.-10 Nov. 1880
    - Vol. 3, 16 Apr.-27 Dec. 1889
    - Vol. 4, 4 Dec. 1889-13 June 1890
    - Vol. 5, 31 Jan.-2 June 1890
    - Vol. 6, 17 July-13 Nov. 1890
    - Vol. 7, 13 Apr.-29 Dec. 1891 (Box 347)
    - Vol. 8, 6 June-17 Nov. 1892
    - Vol. 9, 17 Nov. 1892-3 July 1893
    - Vol. 10, 26 Aug. 1893-19 Mar. 1894
    - Vol. 11, 29 Mar.-17 Oct. 1894 (Box 348)
    - Vol. 12, 23 Oct. 1894-10 Jan. 1895
    - Vol. 13, 12 Jan.-31 July 1895
    - Vol. 14, 3 Aug.-22 Sept. 1895
    - Vol. 15, 14 Oct.-10 Dec. 1895
    - Vol. 16, 10 Dec. 1895-22 May 1896 (Box 349)
    - Vol. 17, 23 May-1 Oct. 1896
    - Vol. 18 not included
    - Vol. 19, 1 Oct. 1896-26 May 1897
    - Vol. 20, 26 May-6 Oct. 1897
    - Vol. 21, 28 Oct.-9 Nov. 1897
    - Vol. 22, 23 Nov. 1897-25 July 1898
    - Vol. 23, 9 Feb.-2 Mar. 1898 (Box 350)
    - Vol. 24, 5 Aug. 1898-29 Apr. 1899
    - Vol. 25, 11 May-22 Sept. 1899
    - Vol. 26, 31 May 1899-25 Aug. 1900
    - Vol. 27, 28 Sept. 1899-17 Oct. 1900 (Box 351)
    - Vol. 28, 16 Nov. 1900-17 Feb. 1901
    - Vol. 29, 19 Feb.-17 June 1901
    - Vol. 30, 25 June-1 Oct. 1901
    - Vol. 31, 2-29 Oct. 1901
    - Vol. 32, 30 Oct. 1901-21 Jan. 1902 (Box 352)
    - Vol. 33, 22 Jan.-20 May 1902
    - Vol. 34, 23 Mar.-8 June 1902
    - Vol. 35, 9 June-30 Sept. 1902
    - Vol. 36, 30 Sept.-6 Dec. 1902
    - Vol. 37, 7 Dec.-2 May 1903 (Box 353)
    - Vol. 38, 6 May-30 June 1903
    - Vol. 39, 1 July-29 Sept. 1903
    - Vol. 40, 30 Sept.-26 Nov. 1903
    - Vol. 41, 26 Nov. 1903-15 Mar. 1904
    - Vol. 42, 18 Mar.-4 June 1904 (Box 354)
    - Vol. 43, 12 June-5 Aug. 1904
    - Index
      - Vols. 30, 32-37, 39-41, 1901-1903
    - Vol. 44, 21 Nov. 1900-10 June 1905
    - Vol. 45, 19 Mar.-18 Aug. 1905
    - Vol. 46, 26 Oct. 1905-1 Feb. 1906 (Box 355)
    - Vol. 47, 1 Feb.-2 June 1906
    - Vol. 48, 24 June-22 Oct. 1906
    - Vol. 49, 24 Oct. 1906-20 June 1907
    - Vol. 50, 20 June-17 Aug. 1907
    - Vol. 51, 18 Aug.-22 Oct. 1907 (Box 356)
    - Vol. 52, 23 Oct.-7 Dec. 1907
    - Vol. 53, 7 Dec. 1907-3 Mar. 1908
    - Vol. 54, 10 Mar.-5 June 1908
    - Vol. 55, 7 July-5 Sept. 1908
    - Vol. 56, 5 Sept.-14 Nov. 1908 (Box 357)
    - Vol. 57, 14 Nov. 1908-7 Feb. 1909
    - Vol. 58, 8 Feb.-14 Apr. 1909
    - Vol. 59, 18 Apr.-17 July 1909
    - Vol. 60, 17 July-29 Aug. 1909
    - Vol. 61, 30 Aug.-5 Oct. 1909 (Box 358)
    - Vol. 62, 6 Oct.-25 Nov. 1909
    - Vol. 63, 27 Nov. 1909-16 Jan. 1910
    - Vol. 64, 20 Jan.-14 Mar. 1910
    - Vol. 65, 15 Mar.-13 Apr. 1910
    - Vol. 66, 16 Apr.-8 July 1910 (Box 359)
    - Vol. 67, 9 July-5 Oct. 1910
    - Vol. 68, 6 Oct. 1910-26 Jan. 1911
    - Vol. 69, 27 Jan.-1 Apr. 1911
    - Vol. 70, 2 Apr.-16 May 1911 (Box 360)
    - Vol. 71, 17 May-21 Aug. 1911
    - Vol. 72, 22 Aug.-24 Dec. 1911
    - Vol. 73, 24 Dec. 1911-15 Apr. 1912
    - Vol. 74, 16 Apr.-27 Aug. 1912 (Box 361)
    - Vol. 75, 28 Aug.-17 Oct. 1912
    - Vol. 76, 17 Oct. 1912-7 Jan. 1913
    - Vol. 77, 8 Jan.-4 May 1913
    - Vol. 78, 4 May-11 Sept. 1913 (Box 362)
    - Vol. 79, 12 Sept.-11 Nov. 1913
    - Vol. 80, 11 Nov. 1913-4 Jan. 1914
    - Vol. 81, 4 Jan.-14 Feb. 1914
    - Vol. 82, 15 Feb.-22 Apr. 1914 (Box 363)
    - Vol. 83, 23 Apr.-4 July 1914
    - Vol. 84, 4 July-9 Sept. 1914
    - Vol. 85, 10 Sept.-20 Oct. 1914
    - Vol. 86, 21 Oct.-8 Dec. 1914 (Box 364)
    - Vol. 87, 8 Dec. 1914-15 Jan. 1915
    - Vol. 88, 15 Jan.-3 Apr. 1915
    - Vol. 89, 4 Apr.-29 June 1915
    - Vol. 90, 30 June-25 Aug. 1915 (Box 365)
    - Vol. 91, 25 Aug.-26 Sept. 1915
    - Vol. 92, 27 Sept.-22 Oct. 1915
    - Vol. 93, 22 Oct.-20 Nov. 1915
    - Vol. 94, 22 Nov. 1915-13 Feb. 1916 (Box 366)
    - Vol. 95, 13 Feb.-27 Apr. 1916
    - Vol. 96, 4 May-28 July 1916
    - Vol. 97, 28 July-15 Sept. 1916
    - Vol. 98, 15 Sept.-2 Nov. 1916 (Box 367)
    - Vol. 99, 3 Nov.-20 Dec. 1916
    - Vol. 100, 20 Dec. 1916-27 Jan. 1917
    - Vol. 101, 28 Jan.-21 Apr. 1917
    - Vol. 102, 21 Apr.-23 May 1917 (Box 368)
    - Vol. 103, 24 May-21 June 1917
    - Vol. 104, 22 June-24 July 1917
    - Vol. 105, 24 July-29 Aug. 1917
    - Vol. 106, 29 Aug.-27 Sept. 1917 (Box 369)
    - Vol. 107, 28 Sept.-12 Nov. 1917
    - Vol. 108, 12 Nov.-28 Dec. 1917
    - Vol. 109, 28 Dec. 1917-2 Feb. 1918
    - Vol. 110, 3 Feb.-23 Apr. 1918 (Box 370)
    - Vol. 111, 1 Apr.-6 Aug. 1918
    - Vol. 112, 6 Aug.-14 Sept. 1918
    - Vol. 113, 15 Sept.-6 Nov. 1918
    - Vol. 114, 7 Nov. 1918-25 Jan. 1919 (Box 371)
    - Vol. 115, 27 Jan.-1 May 1919
    - Vol. 116, 3 May-9 Aug. 1919
    - Vol. 117, 9 Aug.-27 Sept. 1919
    - Vol. 118, 27 Sept.-22 Nov. 1919 (Box 372)
    - Vol. 119, 22 Nov. 1919-22 Jan. 1920
    - Vol. 120, 22 Jan.-8 Mar. 1920
    - Vol. 121, 8 Mar.-4 May 1920
    - Vol. 122, 4 May-21 June 1920 (Box 373)
    - Vol. 123, 22 June-23 July 1920
    - Vol. 124, 24 July-26 Aug. 1920
    - Vol. 125, 26 Aug.-27 Oct. 1920
    - Vol. 126, 28 Oct. 1920-10 Jan. 1921 (Box 374)
    - Vol. 127, 11 Jan.-9 Mar. 1921
    - Vol. 128, 10 Mar.-19 May 1921
    - Vol. 129, 19 May-29 July 1921
    - Vol. 130, 29 July-21 Sept. 1921 (Box 375)
    - Vol. 131, 21 Sept.-14 Nov. 1921
    - Vol. 132, 15 Nov. 1921-16 Feb. 1922
    - Vol. 133, 16 Feb.-13 May 1922 (Box 376)
    - Vol. 134, 15 May-22 Sept. 1922
    - Vol. 135, 9 Aug.-23 Nov. 1922
    - Fragments, n.d.
    - Subject index (Box 377)
      - A-B
      - B-H (Box 378)
      - H-P (Box 379)
      - P-Z (Box 380)
  - Laboratory notes See also Microfilm (Box 381)
    - 6 Dec. 1879-5 Jan. 1880 See Container 394, Vol. 69
    - Vol. 1, 7 Dec. 1879-23 Apr. 1880
    - 4 Mar.-12 May 1880 See Container 395, Vol. 73
    - Vol. 2, 26 Apr.-12 May 1880
    - Vol. 3, 12-19 May 1880
    - 14 May-11 June 1880 See Container 395, Vol. 74
    - Vol. 4, 20 May-1 June 1880
    - Vol. 5, 2-10 June 1880
    - Vol. 6, 10-15 June 1880
    - Vol. 7, 16 June-10 July 1880 (Box 382)
    - Vol. 8, 13-23 July 1880
    - Vol. 9, 23 July-17 Aug. 1880
    - Vol. 10, 20 Aug. 1880-3 Jan. 1881
    - Vol. 11, 4-24 Jan. 1881
    - Vol. 12, 24 Jan.-19 Feb. 1881
    - 19 Feb.-28 Mar. 1881 See Container 395, Vol. 72 (Box 383)
    - Vol. 13, 29 Mar. 1881-12 June 1882
    - Vol. 14, 15 Mar. 1881-1 Aug. 1882
    - Vol. 15, 25 June 1881-29 July 1882
    - Vol. 16, 29 July 1881-1 Jan. 1882
    - Vol. 17, 8 Jan.-1 Aug. 1882
    - Vol. 18, 13 June 1882-11 Jan. 1883
    - Vol. 19, 27 June 1882-23 Mar. 1883 (Box 384)
    - Vol. 20, 29 July 1882-4 May 1886
    - 26 Mar.-22 Aug. 1883 See Container 395, Vol. 75
    - Vol. 21, 6 Dec. 1883-27 Mar. 1884
    - Vol. 22, 1 Jan. 1885-11 Jan. 1887
    - Vol. 23, 28 Nov. 1885-19 Oct. 1887
    - Vol. 24, 19 Feb.-7 Dec. 1887
    - Vol. 25, 24 Dec. 1887-6 Jan. 1888 (Box 385)
    - Vol. 26, 20 Oct. 1887-9 Dec. 1889
    - Vol. 27, 13 Jan.-7 Mar. 1888
    - Vol. 28, 9 Mar. 1888-19 Dec. 1889
    - Vol. 29, 3 Feb.-13 June 1890
    - Vol. 30, 9 Feb. 1890 (Box 386)
    - Vol. 31, 29 Dec. 1891-5 June 1893
    - Vol. 32, 6 June 1893-10 Jan. 1895
    - Vol. 33, 11 Jan.-21 Aug. 1895
    - Vol 34, 21 Aug.-25 Oct. 1895 (Box 387)
    - Vol. 35, 28 Oct.-28 Dec. 1895
    - Vol. 36, 30 Dec. 1895-3 June 1896
    - Vol. 37, 4 June-24 July 1896
    - Vol. 38, 24 July-7 Sept. 1896
    - Vol. 39A, 7 Sept.-30 Oct. 1896 (Box 388)
    - Vol. 39B, 30 Oct.-19 Nov. 1896
    - Vol. 40, 20 Nov. 1896-1 July 1897
    - Vol. 41, 1 July-17 Aug 1897
    - Vol. 42, 4 Aug.-11 Sept. 1897
    - Vol. 43, 18 Aug.-17 Sept. 1897
    - Vol. 44, 14 Sept.-24 Oct. 1897 (Box 389)
    - Vol. 45, 25 Oct.-20 Nov. 1897
    - Vol. 46, 1 June-16 Nov. 1898
    - Vol. 47, 10 May-9 Aug. 1899
    - Vol. 48, 22 Aug.-7 Dec. 1899
    - Vol. 49, 6 Aug.-30 Nov. 1901 (Box 390)
    - Vol. 50, 8 Aug.-30 Nov. 1901
    - Vol. 51, 9 May-27 Sept. 1902
    - Vol. 52, 28 Sept.-9 Dec. 1902
    - Vol. 53, 16 June-25 Nov. 1903
    - Vol. 54, 12 June-5 Oct. 1904 (Box 391)
    - Vol. 55, 18 Mar. 1905-26 Mar. 1906
    - Vol. 56, 5 Oct.-22 Dec. 1905
    - Vol. 57, 12 May-19 Dec. 1906
    - Vol. 58, 22 June 1907-26 Feb. 1909
    - Vol. (unbound), 8 Aug. 1907-21 Feb. 1908
    - Vol. (unbound), 27 Feb. 1908-2 Jan. 1909 (Box 392)
    - Vol. 59, 10 July 1908-3 Mar. 1909
    - Vol. (unbound), 26 Apr.-3 July 1909
    - Vol. 60, 14 July-4 Oct. 1911
    - Vol. 61, 5 Oct.-20 Dec. 1911 (Box 393)
    - Vol. 62, 9 July-10 Sept. 1912
    - Vol. 63, 11 Sept.-20 Nov. 1912
    - Vol. 64, 21 Nov.-9 Dec. 1912
    - Vol. 65, 3 July-12 Nov. 1913 (Box 394)
    - Vol. 66, 13 Nov. 1913-20 July 1914
    - Vol. 67, 21 July-30 Oct. 1914
    - Vol. 68, 31 Oct.-1 Dec. 1914
    - Vol. 69, 6 Dec. 1879-5 Jan. 1880
    - Vol. 70, 7-26 Jan. 1880 (Box 395)
    - Vol. 71, 27 Jan.-4 Mar. 1880
    - Vol. 72, 19 Feb.-28 Mar. 1881
    - Vol. 73, 4 Mar.-12 May 1880
    - Vol. 74, 14 May-11 June 1880
    - Vol. 75, 26 Mar.-22 Aug. 1883
- Article and Book File, 1901-1904, n.d. (Box 395-398)
  Handwritten and typewritten drafts and printed copies of articles and books.
  Grouped by type of material and arranged alphabetically thereunder.
  - Articles (Box 395)
    - "The Adventures of Mr. H. A. Largelamb"
    - "An Aerial Highway to the Pole"
    - "Aerial Locomotion"
    - "Aurora Borealis Observed at Beinn Bhreagh, Near Baddeck, Nova Scotia, Sep. 21 and Oct. 18, 1909"